Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1963-1990; (Contained in 39 Boxes)
  - 95th Congress (), 1977-78
    - List of Bills Sponsored and Cosponsored Bills Cosponsored
      - H.J.Res. 318, National Cancer Prevention Day, September 8th of Each Year. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 4468, National Climate Program Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 166, National Commission on Social Security. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 7376, National Community-Based Organizations Youth Job Creation and Training Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 291, H.J.Res. 292, National Community Health Week (2). (Box 12)
      - H.R. 3108, National Conference on Learning Disabilities and Juvenile Delinquency Act. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 3694, National Consumer Cooperative Bank Act. (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 502, H.J.Res. 950, National Family Week (2). (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 906, National Grandparents Day. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 5403, National Housing Act, Amended, re Geriatric Clinics. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 5082, H.R. 5128, National Labor Relations Act, Amended (2). (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 24, H.J.Res. 971, National Lupus Week (2). (Box 12)
      - H.R. 3004, National Meals-on-Wheels Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 8781, National Park and Seashore in California, re Channel Islands. (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 861, National Port Week. (Box 12)
      - H.J.Res. 936, National Rehabilitation Week. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 13048, No-Fault Benefit Plans for Victims. (Box 12)
      - H.Con.Res. 630, Non-Export of Low-Enriched Uranium to India. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 12767, Smithsonian Institution to Acquire National Museum of African Art. (Box 12)
      - H.Con.Res. 277, Non-Reduction of Postal Deliveries. (Box 12)
      - H.Res. 942, Norwegian Nobel Peace Prize. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 5453, Nursing Home Reform Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 4667, Oil Spill Removal Research, Development, and Demonstration Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 5411, Older Americans Health Services Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 5394, H.R. 12255, Older Americans Act of, Amended (2)., 1965 (Box 12)
      - H.R. 12032, Older Americans Employment Rights Act of, 1978. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 7821, Omnibus Crime Control and Safe Streets Act of, Amended., 1968 (Box 12)
      - H.R. 4313, Older Persons Comprehensive Counseling Assistance Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 5812, Omnibus Intelligence, Community Reorganization and Reform Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 8584, Opportunities for Adoption Act of, 1977. (Box 12)
      - H.R. 10680, Opportunities Industrialization Centers Skills Training Act, etc. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 11576, Opportunities Industrialization Centers, Welfare Reform Act of, 1978. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3438, Opportunities Industrialization Centers Skills Training and National Community Based Organizations Job Creation and Employment Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 6183, Part-Time Career Opportunity Act. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4084, H.R. 4044, Penalty for Robbery or Attempted Robbery of a Pharmacy (2). (Box 13)
      - H.R. 5832, Phase Withdrawal of U.S. Armed Forces from Korea. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 6888, Plutonium Licensing Control Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 384, Popular Election of the President and Vice President of the U.S. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4055, Ports and Waterways Safety Act of, Amended., 1972 (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4516, Postal Employees Collective Bargaining Representation. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 13284, Press Protection Act of, 1978. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 6051, Prevent Abuses of Power by FBI and CIA. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8127, Prevent Abuses of Power by Intelligence Agencies. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 11269, Prohibit Age Discrimination in Employment. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8235, Prohibit Postal Service Mail Service Limitation. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7705, Protection of Medical Records, etc. (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 284, Protection of International Waters. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 14336, Public Employee Retirement Income Security Act of, 1978. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8719, Public Housing Security Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4971, Public Participation in Federal Agency Proceedings Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 9951, Quantification of Federal Reserved Water Rights for Indian Reservations Act. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8691, Radiation Health and Safety Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 593, Recognizing the Contribution of School Volunteers. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4067, Reemployment Services Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7905, Rehabilitation Act of, Amended., 1973 (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 699, Representation for District of Columbia. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 6151, Revised Statutes, Section 1979, Amended. (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 425, H.J.Res. 446, Review of U.S. Practice Embargo to Republic of South Africa (2). (Box 13)
      - H.R. 5934, Roosevelt, Eleanor National Historic Site in State of New York. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 11030, Social Security LIFE Act of, 1978. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3468, Santa Margarita National Recreation Park. (Box 13)
      - H.Res. 72, Select Committee on Population. (Box 13)
      - H.Res. 349, To Establish a Select Committee on Welfare Reorganization. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4393, Service Contract Act of, Amended, re Professional Employees., 1965 (Box 13)
      - H.R. 5386, H.R. 5636, H.R. 7379, H.R. 7528, H.R. 8028, H.R. 8401, Social Security Act, Amended (6). (Box 13)
      - Social Security Act, Amended
        - H.R. 3234, re Supplemental Security Income. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 3483, re Payments to Chiropractors. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 11238, re Title XX. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5398, re Reallotment of Unused Social Services Funds. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 8395, H.R. 2874, H.R. 4598, re Cost-of-Living (3). (Box 13)
        - H.R. 8396, re Title II. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4012, H.R. 4415, re Mailing of Checks (2). (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4212, re Blind Insurance Disability Benefits. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 3917, re Home Health Services. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5835, re Increase Amount of Outside Earnings. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 7072, re Papanicolaou Tests. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5427, re Supplementary Medical Insurance. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4368, re Drugs. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5308, re Registered Nurses for Medicare. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5419, re Long-Term Institution Care. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5450, re Outside Income Limitation. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 5834, re Delayed Retirement. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 3483, re Supplementary Medical Insurance. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 10794, Social Security Act and Internal Revenue Code of, Amended., 1954 (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7483, Social Security Rights Act. (Box 13)
      - H.Con.Res. 720, South African Black Community Crossroads. (Box 13)
      - H.Con.Res. 120, Special Task Force, re Price of Natural Gas. (Box 13)
      - H.Con.Res. 62, Statue of Martin L. King, Jr. in U.S. Capitol. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7476, Standards for No-Fault Motor Vehicle Accident Benefits Act. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8185, Stocks Management and Reserve Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3291, Sugar Disclosure Labeling Act. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 5415, Supplemental Payments Under Home Health Care Service Grants. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7375, Supplemental Security Income Reform Amendments of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 14160, Sunset Program Re-Authorization and Evaluation Act of, 1978. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 5663, Surface Mining Control and Reclamation Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 2458, Surplus School Conservation Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 487, Surplus School Conservation Act of, 1976. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 1041, Tax Equity Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 5015, Tax Reform Act of, Amended., 1976 (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3057, Taxation of Real Property by State and Local Governments. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7467, Telecommunication Devices in the Congress. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8263, Temporary Appointments to Vacancies of Courts (Manner of Appointments). (Box 13)
      - H.R. 65, Terminate Age Discrimination in Employment. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 4129, Time Schedule to Congress from President on Agency Reorganization. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 10375, Title I Amendments Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 12685, H.R. 4460, Trade Act of, Amended (2)., 1974 (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3047, Trading With the Enemy Act. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 8106, Truth in Lending Improvement Amendments of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7507, U.S. Code, Amended. (Box 13)
      - U.S. Code, Amended
        - H.R. 6413, re Title 5. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4820, re Federal Bureau of Investigation. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4819, re Informers. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 3244, re Veterans' Pensions. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 8187, re Veterans and Benefits. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4621, re Veterans of Mexcan Border Period. (Box 13)
        - H.R. 4150, re Utility Stamp Program. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 7696, Urban Grant University Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 10880, Veterans' and Survivors' Pension Improvement Act of, 1978. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3682, Vocational Education Act of, Amended., 1963 (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 428, White House Conference on Aging Act., 1981 (Box 13)
      - H.J.Res. 648, White House Conference on Humanities Act., 1979 (Box 13)
      - H.Con.Res. 277, Reduction of U.S. Mail Delivery Service. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 12107, Wildlife on Federal Lands Trapping Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 3633, Wildlife Restoration Fund Act, re Additional Funds. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 2767, World War I Pension Act of, 1977. (Box 13)
      - H.R. 31, Young Adult Conservation Corps Act. (Box 13)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Education and Labor Committee (2). (Box 13)
      - Elementary and Secondary Education Act. (Box 13)
      - SubCommittee on Manpower and Employment Opportunities. (Box 14)
      - Summary of Major Provisions of H.R. 6138, Youth Employment and Innovative Demonstration Project. (Box 14)
      - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act. (Box 14)
    - Legislative Profile Committee Files
      - Agriculture Committee. (Box 14)
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 14)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 14)
      - Banking and Currency Committee. (Box 14)
      - District of Columbia Committee. (Box 14)
      - Fair Employment Practices Committee. (Box 14)
      - Foreign Affairs Committee. (Box 14)
      - Government Operations Committee. (Box 14)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 14)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 14)
      - Internal Security Committee. (Box 14)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee. (Box 14)
      - Joint Economic Committee. (Box 14)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 14)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee. (Box 14)
      - Miscellaneous. (Box 14)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee. (Box 14)
      - P.O and Civil Service Committee, re H.R. 7700. (Box 14)
      - Public Works Committee. (Box 14)
      - Rules Committee. (Box 14)
      - Science and Technology Committee. (Box 14)
      - Select Committees. (Box 14)
      - Small Business Committee. (Box 14)
      - Veterans' Affairs Committee. (Box 14)
      - Ways and Means Committee. (Box 14)
    - List of Bills Sponsored and Cosponsored. (Box 14)
  - 96th Congress (), 1979-80
    - Bills Sponsored and Cosponsored House Administration Proxy Forms Bills Sponsored
      - H.R. 6796, Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, Amended. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 7238, CETA Appropriations for Fiscal Year, 1981. (Box 15)
      - H.Con.Res. 279, Our American Government Booklet. (Box 15)
      - H.Con.Res. 66, Our Flag Booklets. (Box 15)
      - H.Con.Res. 65, Declaration of Independence and the Constitution of the U.S. Booklets. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 6508, Federal Supplemental Employment Act. (Box 15)
      - P.L 95-523, Full Employment and Balanced Growth Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4426, Work and Training Entitlement Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4425, Work and Training Opportunities Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4465, Youth Employment Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - National Publications Act of, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Bills Cosponsored
      - H.R. 6288, African Development Foundation Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4450, Afro-American Museum Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 70, Age Discrimination in Employment Act of, Amended., 1967 (Box 15)
      - H.R. 7557, Aid to Tuskegee Institute. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 39, Alaska National Interest Lands Conservation Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 6897, Alternative and Worksite Education Act of, 1980. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3282, Asbestos, School Inspection. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 205, Ralph J. Bunche Monument, New York City. (Box 15)
      - H.Con.Res. 413, The Capitol Booklets. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 2975, Channel Islands Marine National Park, California. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5630, Chrysler Corporation Emergency Credit Assistance Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5412, CETA, Amended. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4514, CETA Bill, Amended, re Energy Resources. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3583, CETA, Amended, re Part B. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 2074, Civil Rights Amendments Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5499, Commission on Wartime Relocation and Internment of Civilians Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 498, Congressional Award Program Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3697, Congressional Budget Act, Amended. (Box 15)
      - H.Res. 515, Congressional Child Care Center. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4568, Defense Production Act of, Amended., 1950 (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 477, Walt Disney Proclamation. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 15, Designate Martin Luther King, Jr. as Public Legal Holiday. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5284, District of Columbia Retirement Reform Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 2859, Domestic Volunteer Services Act Amendments of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 7423, Equal Employment Opportunity for the Handicapped Act of, 1980. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 26, Establish Position of Assistant Secretary of Labor. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 7868, Farm Labor Contractor Act of, 1980. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3412, H.R. 4926, Federal Aviation Act of 1958, Amended (2). (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5010, Federal Election Campaign Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 2977, Federal Support and Stimulation, Prevent Domestic Violence. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3393, Federal Reclamation Law, Clarification. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4327, H.R. 6115, General Education Provisions Act, Amended (2). (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3181, Higher Education Act of, Amended, re Urban Universities., 1965 (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4093, Infant Nutrition Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 1246, Intergovernmental Antirecession and Supplementary Fiscal Assistance Amendments of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4767, Internal Revenue Code of, Amended., 1954 (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5409, Internal Revenue Code of, Amended, re Passenger Autos., 1954 (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5004, Daniel James Memorial Center for Preventive Health Education Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 6704, Juvenile Justice Amendments of, 1980. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4531, Lifelong Learning Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 6194, Medicaid Community Care Act of, 1980. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5140, Motor Vehicle Information and Cost Savings Act, Amended. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 7644, Municipal Arts Program Act of, 1980. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 442, National Athletic Boosters Week. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5040, National Employment Priorities Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 263, National Farmworkers' Week. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 68, National Family Week. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 244, National Grandparents Day. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5856, Amend U.S. Code, re National Guard. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 255, National Medic Alert Week. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3578, National Safe Boating Week. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5424, National Publications Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3153, Natural Gas Pricing Amendments Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 1297, Non-Use of Steel Jaw Traps in U.S. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4443, Oil and Gas Tax of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3349, Outstanding Americans Gold Medallion Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4, Older Americans Employment Rights Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4572, Public Printing Reorganization Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3635, H.R. 3992, Social Security Act, Amended (2). (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3390, Social Security Act, Amended, re Supplemental Income. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 3567, Soft Drink Interbrand Competition Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 997, Sound Recording Performance Rights Amendments. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 1421, Surplus School Conservation Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - H.J.Res. 267, Teacher Day, U.S.A. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 5892, Wind Energy Systems Research, Development, and Demonstration Act. (Box 15)
      - H.R. 4897, World Peace Tax Fund Act. (Box 15)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Education and Labor Committee. (Box 15)
      - SubCommittee on Employment Opportunities. (Box 15)
      - Agriculture Committee. (Box 15)
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 15)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 15)
      - Banking, Currency, and Housing Committee. (Box 15)
      - Banking Committee, H.R. 4986, Consumer Checking Account Equity Act of, 1979. (Box 15)
      - Budget Committee. (Box 15)
      - Government Operations Committee. (Box 15)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 15)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 16)
      - International Relations Committee. (Box 16)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee. (Box 16)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, Inflation and Windfall Profits Cards. (Box 16)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 16)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee. (Box 16)
      - Miscellaneous. (Box 16)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee. (Box 16)
      - Public Works and Transportation Committee. (Box 16)
      - Rules Committee. (Box 16)
      - Science and Technology Committee. (Box 16)
      - Small Business Committee. (Box 16)
      - Standards of Official Conduct Committee. (Box 16)
      - Veterans' Affairs Committee. (Box 16)
      - Ways and Means Committee. (Box 16)
      - Select Committee on Aging. (Box 16)
      - Ad Hoc Select Committee on Energy. (Box 16)
    - Black Educators' Conference, March 1980. (Box 16)
    - Education, Constance E. Clayton, School District of Philadelphia. (Box 16)
  - 97th Congress (), 1981-82
    - List of Legislation Legislative Profile Bills Sponsored
      - H.Res. 111, CETA Title II (d). (Box 16)
      - H.R. 6250, Community Renewal Employment Act. (Box 16)
      - P.L. 96/583, Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (H.R. 6796). (Box 16)
      - H.R. 5320, Community Partnership for Employment and Training Act. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 59, Electing Members to Joint Committee for Printing and Library. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 5389, Emergency Youth Employment Tax Incentive Act. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 9, H.Res. 294, Funds for Standing and Select Committees of the House of Representatives (2). (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 414, Gen. Motors Corp. Auto Plants in South Gate and Fremont, California, re Closure. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 75, House Administration Investigation Committee Funding. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 363, House Information Systems Funding. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 3242, Diagne Mamadou, Relief Bill. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 320, Legislative Reorganization Act. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 194, Job Loss in the U.S. Due to Expanded Foreign Production. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 120, Resolution Opposing a Rescission Message Numbered R81-92. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 221, Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 400, Franklin D. Roosevelt Memorial Commission. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 541, Space Shuttle Program. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 5369, Veterans' Burial Bill. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 1646, Youth Employment Act. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 3219, H.R. 3337, Youth Employment Demonstration Amendments of (2)., 1981 (Box 16)
    - Bills Cosponsored
      - H.R. 3602, Adjustment to Refugee Admission Status for Cuban And Haitian Nations in U.S. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 463, Administration's Policy on Unemployment. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 70, Age Discrimination in Employment Amendments of, 1981. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 4332, Air Traffic Controller Act. (Box 16)
      - H.Res. 193, Badzyo, Yuri Resolution. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 4083, California Wilderniess Act of, 1981. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 1454, Civil Rights Amendments Act of, 1981. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 1805, Commercial Use of Sound Recordings Amendments. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 514, Employment and Training Assistance. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 5834, Family Housing Production Act of, 1982. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 6492, Handicapped Infants Protection Act of, 1982. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 3824, H.R. 501, Internal Revenue Code, Amended (2). (Box 16)
      - H.R. 2789, Bizz Johnson Trial. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 3269, Malt Beverage Interbrand Competition Act. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 800, Martin L. King, Jr. Public Holiday. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 4403, Mono Basin Aqueduct. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 516, National Coin Week. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 272, National Medic Alert Week. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 100, Non-Discrimination in Insurance Act. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 5933, Olympic Coin Act of, 1982. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 1765, Petroleum Displacement Act of, 1981. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 3973, Postal Service Amendments of, 1981. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 769, Prevention, Identification, and Treatment of Elder Abuse Act of, 1981. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 6576, Prohibition of Mandatory Retirement and Employment Rights Act of, 1982. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 551, Regulations Relative to Child Employment. (Box 16)
      - H.Con.Res. 45, Resolution in Which U.S., Canada, and Mexico Establish a Common Economic Bond. (Box 16)
      - H.R. 556, Research Modernization Act. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 221, Commemoration of 100th Anniversary of Franklin Delano Roosevelt. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 400, Franklin D. Roosevelt Memorial Commission. (Box 16)
      - H.J.Res. 562, Supplemental Appropriations (Department of Labor). (Box 17)
      - H.R. 3496, Sales Representatives Protection Act. (Box 17)
      - H.R. 7160, Small Business Act, Amended. (Box 17)
      - H.R. 3824, Urban Jobs and Enterprise Zone Act of, 1981. (Box 17)
      - H.R. 2045, Maggie Lena Walker Medal. (Box 17)
      - H.J.Res. 328, Roy Wilkins Day. (Box 17)
      - H.R. 4897, World Peace Tax Fund Act. (Box 17)
      - H.R. 1918, World War I Veterans' Service Pension Act. (Box 17)
      - Cosponsored Bills, To Be Filed. (Box 17)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Education and Labor (2). (Box 17)
      - SubCommittee on Employment Opportunities. (Box 17)
    - Committee Files
      - Agriculture Committee. (Box 17)
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 17)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 17)
      - Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs Committee. (Box 17)
      - Budget Committee. (Box 17)
      - District of Columbia Committee. (Box 17)
      - Foreign Affairs Committee. (Box 17)
      - Government Operations Committee. (Box 17)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 17)
      - House Administration Committee
        - Harper and Williams Police Personnel Matter. (Box 17)
        - Organization Committee Notebook. (Box 17)
        - Caucus Notebook. (Box 17)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 17)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee. (Box 17)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 17)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee. (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous. (Box 17)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee. (Box 18)
      - Franking Commission. (Box 18)
      - Public Works and Transportation Committee. (Box 18)
      - Rules Committee. (Box 18)
      - Science and Technology Committee. (Box 18)
      - Small Business Committee. (Box 18)